Iginari Expedition, Iginari Expedition
This is Stalnus of Ijirog and Iginari Talksarnus.
Pleased to meet you.
This is Kitami Boiled and Karen Fuchihara.
Let me tell you what we'll be doing today.
Oooooo!
Today's exploration is to promote the Sendai T-shirt Festival!
Yay!
Now, as the Sendai T-Shirt Festival is currently underway, we are going to promote the Sendai T-Shirt Festival.
It's a T-shirt festival where companies, influencers, and characters from Miyagi Prefecture make and sell their original T-shirts.
It's a T-shirt festival.
There are a total of 56 kinds of original T-shirts in the store.
There are 56 kinds?
By the way, Iginari Talk is in the "Influencers" section.
Really! It's true! Mr. Talk Iginari is in the influencer's section!
Some of them are saying, "Let's introduce those 56 kinds of T-shirts!
Then, let's introduce the T-shirts!
GO!
So, let's start with the T-shirts...
What's going on? You guys are getting bigger!
You're so full!
Did you eat something?
You're so big. You're so fat. I wonder if it's the shoulder muscles.
Ameta. It's amazing, but, well, we divided the T-shirts we're about to introduce you to between the two of us.
I've asked you to put them all on top of each other. Let's reduce the number of T-shirts as we introduce them.
First, let's start with Ms. Arine.
This T-shirt is from a ground vending machine.
It's nice. The logo is on the chest.
You can wear it normally. It looks like something you would find at a vintage clothing store.
These two T-shirts over here.
Next, then, you must be Kaneru-san, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's Miyagi Television's handsome boy.
The design has quite an impact.
I like it. It's cute. Like a stamp.
Yes, it is.
It says "hotel" on it.
What's wrong?
Oh, Karen.
You eat too much.
Why don't you at least take off your clothes?
Don't let my disciple undress you.
Even if you want to?
I can't.
I don't want to.
It's so tight, the shoulders.
It's like a wetsuit.
Whoa!
Lappin'!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Here comes the second one.
Bo-chan soap!
Cute, Yu-chan!
I like this one.
So cute!
I want this one.
There is another kind of Bocchan soap!
Cute, Yoo-chan!
Cute is not a kanji character.
Cute.
So you're all about additive-free soaps.
It's so good!
It's additive-free soap.
These are the two types. Bocchan soap.
That's Grilli, the character of KHB East Japan Broadcasting.
With eyes, nose, mouth and mustache printed on it?
Yes, Grilli!
That's nice. Why did you stroke it?
Why did you pet him?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's multipolar. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like a miracle collaboration.
Okay, well, now, is this the third one for both of you?
Third one.
Can you take it off yet, one by one?
Alone.
You're getting back to your normal figure.
I'm on a diet.
It's a little simple.It's a little simple, isn't it?
That's Mr. Mau, isn't it?
It's cute. It's very nice.
It's a simple design.
I've seen a lot of white before.
It's a little beige.
There's another color.
It's nice.
I like it.
I want to give it there.
I'm pretty sure my dad wears this kind of thing.
Molino from TBC.
Mr. Molino... "Mr. Molino" sounds like an optimistic change of sketches.
It's a MOLINO T-shirt.
It's nice. Everyone has their own originality and personality.
You can already see the "MOLINO" on the T-shirt.
Here's Lebens.
Lebens T-shirt. This is a photo of Chie Endo in front of Sendai Station, taken decades ago.
Emotional. Yes, it is.
I love it. I'm impressed.
Even back then, we didn't know each other very well.
My grandfather has to go to Sendai now.
It's easier to say "Endo Chain" than "Ewins", isn't it?
That's right.
That's probably true.
If you give it to your grandfather, he'll be impressed.
He's probably from the generation that saw the Endo Chain.
That's nice. Emotional, isn't it?
Emotional.
Nice work, Ewins!
This one is simple.
Endo Chain
I always wear this on my T-shirts.
It's easy to wear.
Sendai Iroha T-shirt by Sendai Broadcasting Co.
Sendai Iro Hajime Sendai
This one is also nice. It's easy to understand.
The one you see often.
Yes, it is. I think it's from a TV program.
I love it! You must be Mr. Bonten Ugoyuki.
Bonten Fish Gyoko-san.
I often go there. Me too.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad that they are so generous.
Bonten Fish Gyoko! Cheers! It's so exciting, isn't it? This drinking party.
I'm sure it would feel great to go out for a beer wearing this.
It's nice.
I want to wear this.
Kahopin, Mr. Kahok Believer!
It's so cute here.
Yes, it is. It looks a little off.
How do you read this? Kane-san.
Bai Gai Kita.
What?
Ippsan hyakubun.
Kahok Believer.
I don't know. What's the right answer?
I don't know either.
I don't know.
What is it?
Shirakawa. It definitely has a meaning.
What do you think it means? Let me tell you.
The White River.
There are others.
Hitami Rine...
Hitami is the best
Like a mountain
High and proud and a hundred points
A woman who can make Wilsham
Wow!
You too, Kitami!
Isn't that a Kitami Line T-shirt?
When Ieyashinpo-san had me
Why is there such a connection?
The correct answer is
I just looked up the meaning
Shirakawa
It's called Shirakawa Crossing.
The northern area, that is, the northeastern area...
There are only about 1,000 gates in this area.Only about a hundred gates of this Senzan
in the sense that there are only about a thousand gates in the Nenai area.
Well
There's a lot going on here.
It looks like there's something going on here.
Cool!
This is cool.
You said you knew how to read it.
Yes, yes, yes.
When you sew this on, it goes like this.
You're going diagonally.
It's a first-magnitude star, and then we get to know each other.
That's how it's done.
Thanks for the tip.
I'm gonna go get a drink with you.
I don't think so.
I think it's Saarine.
It's a Handaya T-shirt!
Doburi-meshi!
I've had this sign in my store since I was a little girl!
Handaya's
I wonder what this girl is doing now.
I wonder for sure.
Isn't this cute?
It's so cute!
There's another one that's really impressive.
There's another kind.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
I have an image of the signboard for this.
Hanada Ya-ha
It has a great impact.
Okay, thank you very much.
Knot Circle T-shirt
This one has a simple knot circle in the center.
A rice ball is eating a rice ball.
So cute!
Now that you mention "eating" together...
This one is simple and easy to wear.
Easy to wear
Nice!
It's a bee!
The back of this one is cute.
Cute!
Bee Neapolitan!
Delicious!
So fashionable!
Like vintage clothes.
What does it say?
Kane-san's English
Welcome to...
Oh, Sendai?
Oh!
It's not Tokyo.
I said Sendai.
What does it say under there?
Nepapottyn?
Hamburger steak.
Oh, it's Neapolitan!
Neapolitan hamburger steak.
And...
Mae.
Mae?
Moo... Moo... More...
Moo-ree?
Moo-ha!
There's "Moo-ha".
I know what it means.
If you can speak Japanese, you know what it means.
Yeah, yeah.
A Tohoku ZUNKO T-shirt.
Ta-da!
You often come to Eavins and hold events.
Very cute!
Both of them are cute!
Tohoku-Dunko, like this tree...
So cute!
Very cute!
This one...This way.
Ah, here we are.
Mr. Kisuke the Beef Tongue, isn't it?
Mr. Kisuke!
So cool!
It looks like something a waiter would wear in a store.
You can wear it now.
The back is plain, and that's it.
I like it.
On the contrary, it's nice.
It's nice. It's simple and cool.
It's definitely simple and cool.
There's something different and cool about it.
Wow, I want to wear this at the store.
I like it.
Sendai-ben KOKESHI T-shirt.
Cute.
You should be a little more impatient.
I've already accepted it.
But first of all, I've already accepted it.
What do you mean by "first"?
See you later.
It's "sendai-ben", isn't it?
Mosaraku-sara-sara.
Mosaraku-sara?
What is this? He doesn't understand.
I think it means "Mosasara-kusasara.
Don't be lazy, get on with it.
Yes, yes, yes.
By the way, do you think so too?
I think so.
Mosasara-kusasara is correct.
It seems to be moving slowly.
Then you're right.
That's nice.
It's nice.
It's like a cloud in the sky.
It's all right.
Saiho! - Saiho! - Saiho!
It's written "Suiho".
It's cool.
It looks like a sports manufacturer.
Yes, it is.
You already know this one.
If it's a great dog...
Everyone knows it.
Everyone knows this zelkova.
I love it.
I didn't know zelkova didn't wear a top.
Really?
I thought you didn't wear clothes.
Clothed or not?
It's a tree.
Yeah, but they're wearing pants.
You've got a little part on you.
Both of them. There's one on each side.
Oh, yeah.
Can we stop this?
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
What?
Can we stop this for a second?
It's Zui Hou, right?
Please tell me you're not stopping.
Wait a minute.
Do you want to stop?
Zui Hou, right?
That's right!
It's cute.
I see. If you're from out of town, for example...
If you're from out of town, you wouldn't understand.
Like this.
You're a jerk, aren't you?
I'm a Miyagi resident, so it's normal for me.
You say "zui hou" as a matter of course because you're from Miyagi Prefecture.
That's funny.
It's a quiz-style T-shirt.
It's fun.
I like the playful spirit.
Come to Miyagi!
It's a "Come to Miyagi" T-shirt!
You're writing again!You're writing again.
What am I writing?
Let me put on my top.
It's an Acme Grand Hotel T-shirt.
Red.
It's cool.
Like the Angels.
Heh.
It's not "heh.
It's delicious, too.
I'm just saying it's like...
They won't know. They won't know.
They'll know.
When your fans see it, they'll know.
I like it. It's very stylish.
You can wear it for everyday.
That's right.
Zunda-kun T-shirt
Zunda-kun.
Zunda-kun
That character was attached to you.
Mr. Zunda
Isn't everyone calling you "Mr. Zunda"?
That's right, Mr. Zunda.
It was Zunda-kun.
It was Zunda-kun, wasn't it?
Was your Twitter name "Zunda-kun"?
I'm pretty sure I changed it this time.
It's just "zunda".
It's so digital.
I guess so.
Cute.
And this one too.
They have names.
Not Akiho.
It's "Autumn rain." How cute.
I know it's not in quiz form, but you can't read "Akisame" either.
Unless you're from Miyagi.
Dundas.
You really want to say it, don't you?
It's cute.
Rine's is Buffalo Dog.
That's youtuber buyer Takahashi's.
It's the one you see in a lot of videos.
I guess it's called "wow" by the people who watch his channel.
I don't have to tell you.
It says "ebe" on it.
I like it.
And Benny Land.
It's bouncy, it's bouncy, it's bouncy, it's bouncy, it's bouncy.
I mean...
Ya-ya-ya-ya.
Everybody can sing
They love you
I can't help but do the buffalo dog thing.
That's cool.
It's a little different.
Buffalo Dog specializes in steaks.
It's like a steakhouse logo.
It's like, "You've had good beef.
It looks like meat.
Mr. Rinne's is more...
It's written on it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I've seen this before.
President Nagano, right?
He's on tiktok youtube.
He's very active on tiktok and youtube.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
The video that starts with the first "tsk tsk" is very famous.
I'm famous for it.
I've never met you.
But if you take a deliberate and mocking shot
We can collaborate on our own.
You should formally apply.
It's like an appeal.
They'll do it.
Where's the appeal?
It's a Dashiro T-shirt.
It says "Dashiro" on it.It says "Dashiro" on it.
That's cool.
It's cool and stylish.
It's fashionable
Celebration Festival
Like an event T-shirt
Like an event T-shirt.
It's like a live T-shirt.
You can't just wear it to work.
Something with a bathing suit on it.
Like, "Don't wear your mom's t-shirt, it's dangerous.
It's fun.
I've got a video that I've been working on.
I don't know if you can call it a title.
This one has the name of the restaurant on it.
I see a lot of dashiros.
I see it a lot.
I'd like to go out to eat wearing this!
Kashisu Orange T-shirt
So cute!
One point
Picktocker's
Faraway's Kaya and Yuna also collaborated
They collaborated with each other, didn't they?
in front of Sendai station
He said he was kind.
That T-shirt.
So cute!
I want to use it normally.
It's a tea igeta T-shirt.
Kikufuku!
So cute!
What kind of back coat is this?
Can you read it?
Kikufuku is a great souvenir or something.
For people all over Japan.
It appears in cartoons and so on.
I'm sure many people are interested in it.
It's delicious.
When I see this, I want to get bored.
Black is good too.
Simply the black version.
Cassis orange. Black and white.
Cute!
Lovely design.
Here's a kikufuku.
It's true!
Cute!
It's very well designed.
The inside is a kikufuku.
In the middle.
It's Moe-chan's T-shirt, isn't it?
Hoyaa!
You've made it into something artistic.
Cool!
Throwing it by hand.
Like a work of art.
It's so cool.
You're doing it.
It's fine.
It's the Ishinomaki connection, isn't it?
This is really cute!
It's Ki no Ya Ishinomaki Fisheries, isn't it?
What's going on with this?
Here's Mr. Gold Coin.
Here's a picture of Mr. Gold Coin.
It's very well designed.
Interesting!
It could be worn as a T-shirt.
It's nice.
This one is simply too.
Hoya color orange.
And..,
It's a gag of Moe-chan.
Hoya Hoya.
Gaggy is written on it.
Cute.
Ki no Ya-san is so cute too.
Cute!
Whale is whale. Ki no Ya-san's canned food is
Whale is famous for whale.They are famous for their whales.
Canned whale.
It has an American feel.
It's like American casual.
It's totally different.
Both are nice.
Suddenly, the Ishinomaki Shu is amazing.
The picture.
It's the last one.
And the next is the last.
The last of a total of 56 types.
The one to decorate,
Se-no!
Yes!
I can't see it, it's so tiny.
What is it? There's some kind of trash on your chest. Both of you.
What? Wait a minute.
There's lint on it. On your chest.
It's not lint.
There's lint on it.
This is lint.
Oh, no?
I can't get it off.
This is a little bit close.
Well, it's an Inari Northeast Samphire, isn't it?
Last one!
Oh no!
What is this design?
Isn't it too tiny?
Rumor has it that they wanted to make it even smaller.
You're still the same.
It's still so crazy.
Oh, it's interesting.
Did you order the logo to be as small as possible?
We often hear from our members that it is easier to wear if the logo is small, or that it is hard to tell that the logo is Tohoku San,
We often said that if the logo was small, it would be easier to wear, or if the logo was hard to recognize as Tohoku Sun, we would be able to wear it to lessons as is.
So, I think they took that into consideration.
Why are you thinking about it?
Because this is a contemporary T-shirt festival.
No, so maybe.
It's not that it's easy to wear to lessons.
We'll be wearing a lot of them, so maybe matching, matching?
No, but it would be better to have the name on the bottom of the T-shirts that we normally wear, so that it stands out a bit.
But it's cute from a fashion point of view. It's cute from a fashion point of view.
It's almost embarrassing.
No, it's an appeal.
On the contrary, it's a little worrisome.
Many people write big on these signs, don't they?
So we decided to be humble and write the names of nine people in small letters at the end.
If we do that, it looks like we are dissing those who write big signatures.
No, we don't.
Oh, really?
Because that's what you're doing now, isn't it?
No, we're not.
What are you going to do with this?
It says "yoga yoga" in big letters.
It's okay.
We're not that good yet,
Humble?
We are just trying to express that kind of feeling, so when we get bigger, we will probably have a logo like this,
The first love is lost.
Yes, the first time will slip away.
Let's keep it in our hearts.
I'm sure it was just a blunder on the part of the management.
Why do the members have to explain themselves? Why do the members have to explain themselves like this?
That's the funny part.
But it's interesting, the idea.
I like it.
I'm interested in it.
It's sporty.
I thought I'd just cut it up.
And then there are the Inari Tohoku-san T-shirts, in black and white, two kinds.
So, we have introduced 1056 types of the Chiyo T-shirt Festival.
Yay!
That was amazing.
Back to normal.
Good, good, good.
I wrote here that it's full of local love,
I really felt the local love.
It was a lot of fun.
The sales period at the apres by individuality, right?The period of sale in apres by individuality is,
April 28 to May 31, 2023.
I can be entrusted with the application on the dedicated website,
I heard that you can get points if you buy a T-shirt.
I see.
Yes, so you can check your points on the website,
I would like to get some recommendations of my favorite stores and so on.
So everything is a flat fee of 2,500 yen, tax included.
That's right.
That's cheap.
You can buy 1,000 kinds, right?
It's okay!
That's good.
I really hope everyone will check it out.
So, that was today's introduction of T-shirts for the prefecture T-shirt festival!
Thank you very much.
Please check it out!
See you soon!
Bye-bye!